Guys,look! Ugly Naked Guy's putting stuff in boxes.
你們看，丑裸男在收拾東西
I'd say our naked buddy is moving.
看樣子我們的裸友要搬家了
Ironically,most of the boxes seem to be labeled "Clothes."
諷刺的是大部分的箱子 都標示著「衣服」
I'm going to miss that big old squishy butt.
我會懷念那個大屁股的
And we're done with the chicken fried rice.
雞肉炒飯沒了
If he's moving,maybe I should try to get his place!
如果他要搬走 我可以去把那裡租下來
It would be so cool to live across from you guys.
好主意 跟你們遙遙相對多好玩啊
We could do that telephone thing...
那我們就可以玩電話遊戲
...where you have a can, we have a can...
你一個罐子，我們一個罐子
...and it's connected by a string.
中間有一條線
Or we could do the actual telephone thing.
或者我們也可以打真的電話
He's got packing tape stuck to where you really don't want it.
糟糕，他的第三點黏到膠帶了
Get it off,fat man! Get it off!
快撕掉啊，肥仔
Oh,no,he's trying to pull it off slowly.
糟糕，他想慢慢撕下來
Take it from me,if you're gonna pull tape off yourself,it's gotta be in one quick motion.
相信我，撕膠帶一定要快狠準
Like that.
就像那樣
The One Where Everyone Finds Out
本集播出：「爾虞我詐」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Oh,my God. I love this apartment!
天哪，我愛死這層公寓了
Isn't it perfect?
很完美吧？
I can't believe I never realized how great it is!
我居然沒發現這裡有這麼棒
Because your eye goes to the big naked man.
因為你的目光 會馬上移到丑裸男身上
It's amazing!
太棒了
Hurry up with an application, or I'll beat you to it.
你最好趕快去申請 否則我會搶先
Well,I'm going to use Ugly Naked Guy's bathroom.
沒想到會有這一天 我要去用丑裸男的衛生間了
Look! There's Monica and Chandler.
你看，是摩妮卡和錢德
Hey,you guys! Hey.
喂，你們好，喂
Chandler and Monica!
錢德和摩妮卡
Oh,my God!
天哪
錢德和摩妮卡！
Oh,my eyes!
我要瞎了！
My eyes!
我要瞎了
It's okay!
菲比，沒事的
-They're doing it! -I know!
不！他們搞在一起 我知道
-I know! -You know?
我知道 你知道？
Yes,I know it. Joey knows, but Ross doesn't,so stop screaming!
對，我知道，喬伊也知道 但羅斯不知道 所以你別再叫了
What's going on?
怎麼了？
-What? -Nothing!
怎麼了？ 沒事
We are so excited that you'll get this apartment!
我們只是好興奮你要搬來這裡
Looks really good.
這裡的確很棒
Looks pretty good!
非常棒
Get in here! Come on!
快過來啊
中央咖啡館
You mean whenever Monica and Chandler...
你是說每次摩妮卡和錢德
...were doing laundry or going grocery shopping?
去洗衣服或買東西或....
The time Monica spent on the phone with Linda from camp?
她每次跟傷心的琳達講電話
Doing it,doing it,phone,doing it.
嘿咻，嘿咻，色情電話
I can't believe it!
真不敢相信
I think it's great. For him.
真是太好了…對男方來說
She could do better.
女方可以有更好的對象
Hey,you guys.
你們好
Come here! What?
喬伊，快過來 怎樣？
Phoebe found out about Monica and Chandler.
菲比發現摩妮卡和錢德的事了
You mean how they're friends and nothing more?
就是他們是朋友，如此而已？
Joey, she knows.
不，喬伊，她知道了
We saw them doing it through the window.
我們剛才在丑裸男的公寓 看到他們隔著窗戶在做
Actually,we saw them doing it up against the window.
應該說是靠著窗戶在做
We saw them fornicating.
我們看到他們私通
So they know you know, and they don't know that Rachel knows?
他們知道你知道 但是不知道瑞秋知道？
Yes,but it doesn't matter who knows what.
對，但現在這些都不重要了
Now enough of us know that we could just tell them we know.
我們有三個人知道 就可以告訴他們了
All the lying and the secrets will finally be over.
我再也不必為了保密而說謊了
Or,we could not tell them we know, and have a little fun.
或者我們也可以不告訴他們 自己來找點樂子
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
If they say they are doing laundry, we'll give them laundry to do.
譬如每次他們說要洗衣服 我們就給他們一堆衣服洗
I would enjoy that.
我喜歡
You know what would be even more fun? Telling them.
你知道怎樣更好玩？ 告訴他們
-That doesn't sound like fun. -So we'll make it fun.
聽起來不好玩 那就讓它變好玩
We'll do it like a barbershop quartet!
我們可以學理髮店四重唱
We know,we know,we know
我們知道…
No,I want to do Phoebe's thing.
不，我想照菲比的做法
I can't take
我沒辦法再…
You don't have to do anything. Just don't tell them we know.
你只要別說我們知道就行了
No. I can't take anymore secrets.
不要，我沒辦法再保密了
I got your secrets,their secrets, secrets of my own.
我有你們的秘密，他們的秘密 還有我自己的秘密
You don't have any secrets.
你才沒有秘密
Well, you don't know about Hugsy, my bedtime penguin pal.
是嗎？你就不知道 我有個企鵝抱枕叫抱寶
How are we going to mess with them?
所以…我們要怎麼耍他們？
You could use your position as the roommate.
你可以利用室友的身份
And I would use the strongest tool at my disposal.
我就運用我最大的本錢
My sexuality.
我的性感
Hello,children.
孩子們
Watch. Learn. And don't eat my cookie.
仔細看，學著點 別吃我的餅乾
That jacket looks great on you.
你穿這件外套真好看
-Really? -The material is so soft.
是嗎? 這個料子摸起來好軟…
Hello,Mr. Bicep.
二頭肌先生
You're working out?
你有在健身嗎？
I try to squeeze things.
我有在擠牙膏
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
If you really want to know
如果你真的想知道
I can't tell you this.
我不能告訴你
You can tell me anything.
菲比，你什麼都可以告訴我
Actually,you are the one person I can't tell this to.
事實上我就是不能告訴你
And the one person I want to the most.
但我又最想告訴你
What's going on?
怎麼了？
I just haven't been with a guy in so long...
因為我很久沒跟男人在一起了
...and sometimes you're looking for something...
有時你一直尋尋覓覓
...and it's right there in front of you,sipping coffee....
卻沒發現他就在你眼前喝咖啡
Oh,no. Have I said too much?
我說太多了嗎？
Just something to think about. I know I will.
總之你考慮一下，我就會考慮
You are so cute.
你好可愛
How did you get to be so cute?
你怎麼會這麼可愛？
My grandfather was Swedish.
我爺爺是瑞典人
And my grandmother was a tiny little bunny.
我奶奶其實是只拇指兔
Now you're even cuter.
你變得更可愛了
-You know,that is a popular opinion today,I must say. -What?
這簡直是今天的民意 什麼？
The weirdest thing happened at the coffeehouse.
今天在咖啡館有一件怪事
I think Phoebe was hitting on me.
我覺得菲比在釣我
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
I'm telling you I think Phoebe thinks I'm foxy.
是真的，菲比覺得我很有魅力
It's not possible.
不可能
I'm sorry,Phoebe's just always thought you were charming...
抱歉，只是在菲比眼中
...in a sexless kind of way.
你的迷人是無性的
You know,I can't hear that enough.
這種話真是百聽不厭
I'm sorry, I just think you misunderstood her.
抱歉，你應該誤解她的意思了
No, I didn't,okay? She was all over me.
我沒有誤解，好嗎？ 她只差沒撲上來
She touched my bicep, for crying out loud.
她還摸我的二頭肌尖叫
This bicep?
這個二頭肌？
Well,it's not flexed right now.
是我現在沒擠它
Why is it so hard for you to believe that Phoebe could be attracted to me?
為什麼你這麼難相信 菲比對我有意思？
It's not.
我沒有啊
All the girls are attracted to you.
女生都會對你有意思
You're part bunny.
你有拇指兔的血統
Mon, What are you doing now? you want to come see a movie with us?
摩妮卡，你要幹什麼？ 要不要一起去看電影？
Actually,I was going to do some laundry.
事實上我正要去洗衣服
Want to do it with me?
錢德，要不要一起去？
Sure,I'll do it with you.
好啊，我跟你一起去
Okay,great. Hold on a second.
太好了，等一下
Here you go.
拿去
That would really help me out a lot. Thanks.
不介意吧？這樣我就輕鬆多了 謝謝
You know what? I don't have enough quarters.
我的硬幣應該不夠
I have quarters!
我這裡有
Great. Now we can do laundry all night. All night laundry!
太好了 我們可以洗一整晚的衣服了
Hey,any word on the apartment yet?
羅斯，公寓申請得怎樣？
I called there,and it turns out Naked Guy is subletting it.
我打過去問 原來丑裸男要自己轉租
He's already had 100 applicants.
而且已經有一大堆申請者
-Oh,man. -No,no,it's okay.
沒關係
Because you know what the difference between them and me is?
我跟他們的差別是…
Your history of bedwetting?
你有尿床的歷史？
Hey,I trusted you,man!
你怎麼可以說出來
Anyway,the difference is...
總之差別是...
...I've got the edge.
我佔了優勢
It's not exactly ethical, but I sent him a bribe...
我知道這樣有點奸詐 但我送了點東西...
...to tip the scales in my direction.
...去賄賂他
You can see it from the window.
從窗戶搞不好看得到
-Is it that pinball machine with the big bow on it? -No.
是那個打了蝴蝶結的彈珠檯嗎 不是
-That new mountain bike? -No.
那輛新的登山車？ 不是
What did you send?
那你送什麼？
A basket of mini muffins.
一籃小英式鬆餅
There's a whole table of them. Which one did you send?
但桌上全都是小英式鬆餅 哪一籃是你送的？
The small one.
小的那一籃
You actually thought that basket was going to get you the apartment?
什麼？你真以為那籃鬆餅 能幫你爭取到公寓？
Someone sent us a basket at work, and people went crazy over those muffins.
對，我們辦公室曾經收到一籃 大家都愛得不得了
It was the best day.
那天真的很高興
Your work makes me sad.
你的工作讓我覺得好悲慘
Oh, man, I want that place so much!
真是的，我好想要那層公寓
And I was so sure that was going to work.
我還以為一定會成功
There's 12 bucks I'll never see again.
那12塊算是丟到水裡了
We'd better go if we want to catch that movie.
菲比，想看電影就得快了
Bye.
再見
Bye, Chandler. I miss you already.
錢德再見，我已經開始想你了
Did you see that? The inappropriate, and the pinching?
你看到她嗲哩嗲氣還捏我嗎？
Actually,I did.
我看到了
So do you believe that she's attracted to me?
你相信她對我有意思了吧？
Oh,my God! She knows about us!
天哪，她知道我們的事了？
Are you serious?
真的還假的？
She knows,and she's trying to freak us out!
菲比知道了，她想嚇我們
That's the only explanation!
這是唯一的解釋
But what about my pinchable butt and my bulging biceps?
那我好捏的屁股 和激凸的二頭肌呢？
She knows!
她知道了
Joey!
喬伊
Yeah?
怎樣？
Phoebe knows about us.
菲比知道我們的事了
I didn't tell them!
我沒告訴她們
Them?
她們？
Who's "them"?
她們是誰？
Phoebe and Joey.
菲比和喬伊
Joey!
喬伊
And Rachel.
和瑞秋
I would have told you, but I promised not to tell.
我想告訴你們 但她們逼我不能說
I'm sorry.
天哪 對不起，
But it's over now,right?
那現在沒事了吧？
You can tell them you know they know, and I can go back to knowing nothing!
你們可以告訴她們你們知道了 我就可以恢復我狀況外的本色
Unless
除非…
Not "unless"! This must end now!
沒有除非，現在就要了結
They think they are so slick messing with us.
她們還自以為高明
But they don't know that we know that they know.
她們不知道我們知道她們知道
So
所以…
The messers become the messees!
沒錯，耍人的變成被耍的
Come on, you guys. Think how much fun it would be to tell.
拜託啦，說出來多好玩
We know,we know,we know
我們知道…
What?
什麼？
Oh, that wasn't you.
對喔，你們不知道
Honey,you got to stop torturing yourself.
不 羅斯，別再折磨自己了
Why don't you find another apartment?
你去找別的房子嘛
I've already looked at 1000 apartments this month.
我這個月已經看了上千個房子
None of them even compares to that one.
沒有一間比得上那一間
Well,except for one,but I would have had to share it with an Armenian family.
有一間不錯但是我得跟 一家亞美尼亞人一起住
Grandma really liked me.
那個奶奶很喜歡我
But I want Ugly Naked apartment!
但我想要丑裸男的公寓
You know what you should do?
你知道你應該怎麼做？
You should find out his hobbies and use that to bond with him.
你應該找出他的嗜好 拿來跟他套交情
Like if I wanted something from Joey...
例如我對喬伊有所求
...I would strike up a conversation about sandwiches...
我就會聊…三明治
...or my underwear.
或是我的內衣
I'm listening.
我在聽
That is a great idea!
看吧 好棒的主意
And I know Ugly Naked Guy because we've been watching him for five years.
而且我瞭解丑裸男 因為我們偷窺了他5年
So that gives me back my edge!
所以我又重新佔了上風
Let's see now. He had the trampoline.
好，他有一張跳床
He broke that.
被他跳壞了
-He had gravity boots. -He broke those too.
他有一雙重力靴 也被他穿壞了
So he likes to break stuff.
所以他喜歡破壞東西
I've got to go pick up Ben. But I will figure something out.
好，我得去接班 不過我會想出來的
Didn't he used to have a cat?
他之前不是有一隻貓？
I wouldn't bring that up. It would bum him out.
別提那個，會害他心情不好
Poor cat never saw that big butt coming.
可憐的貓咪 沒看到大屁股壓下來
喂？
Hold on a second, she's right here.
在，等一下，她就在旁邊
It's Chandler.
錢德找你
Hello,you.
你好
Phoebe, I've been thinking about you all day.
菲比，我一整天都在想你
You know that thing you said before? I was intrigued.
你之前的提議 說我不心動是騙人的
Really?
是嗎？
Joey won't be here tonight.
對，喬伊晚上不在
Why don't you come over? I'll let you feel my bicep.
你要不要過來 我讓你摸我的二頭肌
Or maybe more.
甚至是別的地方
I'll have to get back to you on that. Okay, bye.
我待會再給你答覆，再見
He wants me to come over and feel his bicep and more!
天哪，他找我去摸他的二頭肌 和別的地方
-Are you kidding? -No!
不會吧？ 是真的
I cannot believe he would do that to Mon
他居然背著摩妮卡…
Joey? Do they know that we know?
喬伊，他們知道我們知道嗎？
-No. -Joey!
不知道 喬伊
They know you know.
他們知道你們知道了
I knew it!
我就知道
I would say,"Thank God! Everybody knows! It's finally over!"
我本來會說：謝天謝地 大家都知道了，總算沒事了
But that hasn't been working for me.
但每次說都沒用
I cannot believe those two!
那兩個人真扯
They thought they could mess with us? Trying to mess with us?
他們以為他們可以耍我們 想耍我們是吧？
They don't know that we know they know we know.
他們不知道我們知道 他們知道我們知道了
Joey,you can't say anything.
喬伊，你不能說
Couldn't if I wanted to.
我也不想說了
Good evening,sir. I'm Ross Geller. I'm one of the applicants.
你好，我是羅斯蓋勒 我也申請要租你的房子
I realize that the competition is fierce but....
我知道競爭很激烈，但是…
I'm sorry, I can't help but notice that you're naked.
抱歉，我注意到你光著身體
I applaud you.
我為你鼓掌
Man,I wish I was naked.
我也好想光著身體
I mean,this looks so great.
看起來好舒服
That is how God intended it.
這正是上帝造人的本意
Look. They're panicked!
你看她們多慌
They'll totally back down.
她們絕對會退縮 沒錯
If he wants a date, he's going to get a date.
好，他敢約我就敢去
I'm going to go in.
我要過去了
Be sexy.
性感一點
Please.
拜託
I'd love to come by tonight.
錢德，我晚上可以過去
Really?
真的？
Absolutely. Say,around 7?
當然，就7點吧？
Yes.
好
Good. I'm really looking forward to you and me having sexual intercourse.
很好 我很期待跟你發生性關係
Hey,check it out!
快來看！
Naked Guy's got a naked friend.
丑裸男有裸友來訪
Oh, yeah.
真的
Oh,my God! That's our friend!
天哪，那是我們的朋友
It's Naked Ross!
是裸羅斯
Would you like another mini muffin?
你還要小英式鬆餅嗎？
Try the blueberry,they're delicious.
吃吃看藍莓口味，很好吃
Showtime!
上場羅
-Rachel,get me perfume. -Ok.
瑞秋，拿香水來 好
Joey, can you get me a bottle of wine and glasses?
喬伊，幫我拿一瓶酒兩個酒杯
All right,thanks,but glasses that do not have handles and that are glass.
謝謝，但我要的是 沒把手的玻璃杯
And wine that is not olive oil.
我要酒不要橄欖油
You just make her think you want to have sex with her and it will freak her out.
放心好了 只要讓她以為你想跟她上床 她絕對會嚇到
How far am I gonna have to go with her?
我到底得撐到什麼程度？
Relax, she'll give in way before you do.
別緊張，她會比你先投降
How do you know?
你怎麼知道？
Because you're on my team. My team always wins.
因為你跟我同一隊 我這一隊總是贏
At this?
贏這種事？
Just go get some! Go!
總之去嚇她，快去
Now,I'm going to try to listen from right here.
好，我會站在門外聽 好
Oh,wait.
等一下
Good idea.
好主意
Don't give away the farm.
等等 別把料都爆光了
菲比
Come on in.
錢德 進來吧
I was going to.
我正要進去
I brought some wine. Would you like some?
我帶了酒來，你要嗎？
Sure.
好啊
So here we are.
總算要開始了
Nervous?
緊張嗎？
Me? No. You?
我？不會，你呢？
I want this to happen.
不會，這樣正合我意
So do l.
我也是
I'm going to put on some music.
我去放點音樂
Joey likes to scare the duck.
喬伊喜歡嚇鴨子
Maybe I'll dance for you.
我跳舞給你看好了
You look good.
你真美
Thanks.
謝謝
You know,when you say things like that,it makes me...
你說這種話 讓我...
...want to rip that sweater vest right off.
好想扯掉你的毛衣背心
Why don't we move into the bedroom?
不如進房裡再說吧？
Really?
真的嗎？
Do you not want to?
你不想嗎？
First I want to take off all my clothes...
不是，只是我想先脫掉衣服
...and have you rub lotion on me.
讓你替我擦乳液
That would be nice.
聽起來不錯
I'll go get the lotion.
我去拿乳液
It's way out of hand. She wants me to put lotion on her!
情況完全失控了 她要我幫她擦乳液
-She's bluffing! -She's not backing down.
她在唬你 她沒打算放棄
She went like this
她還這樣
He's not backing down. He went to get lotion.
他沒打算放棄，他去拿乳液了
It's Chandler. You can take him.
他是錢德，你可以搞定他
Come on. Don't you remember when you made him cry using only your words?
還記得你曾經把他罵哭嗎？
Aren't you guys done yet?
真是的，你們還沒好嗎？
I want to sit in my chair!
我想坐我的椅子
The sooner Phoebe breaks him,the sooner it's over and out in the open.
喬伊，菲比一突破錢德的心防 這一切就結束公開了
I like that.
我喜歡
Show him your bra. He's afraid of bras. Can't work them.
我知道，讓他看你的胸罩 他怕胸罩，他解不開
Joey!
喬伊
You didn't rip off any buttons.
你沒把扣子都挑開
It's not my first time.
老經驗了
Go back there and seduce her till she cracks!
你給我回去，色誘她讓她屈服
Give me a second.
好，等一下
-Did you clean up in here? -Of course!
你打掃過嗎？ 當然！
You're going?
你要走了？
Not without you,lover.
除非你跟我走，愛人
So this is my bra.
這是我的胸罩
It's very,very nice.
很好看
Well,come here.
過來
I'm very happy we're going to have all the sex.
我很高興我們要做愛了
You should be. I'm very bendy.
你是該高興，我的身體很柔軟
I'll kiss you now.
我要吻你了
Not if I kiss you first.
除非我先吻你
I guess there's nothing left for us to do but kiss.
接下來就只能接吻了
Here it comes.
終於來了
Our first kiss.
我們的初吻
You win!
好，你贏了
I can't have sex with you!
我不能跟你上床
-And why not? -I'm in love with Monica!
為什麼？ 因為我愛摩妮卡
You're what?
你什麼？
Love her! That's right！
沒錯，我愛她
I...LOVE...HER!
我，愛她
I love her!
我愛她！
I love you,Monica.
我愛你，摩妮卡
I love you too,Chandler.
我也愛你，錢德
I thought you were doing it. I didn't know you were in love!
我以為你們只是搞在一起 我不知道你們相愛
Dude!
兄弟
Hats off to Phoebe. Quite a competitor.
向菲比致敬，強勁的對手
May I say your breasts are still showing.
此外你的胸部還晾在外面
God.
天哪
All right! So that's it?
就這樣
It's over. Everybody knows!
結束了 大家都知道了
Actually,Ross doesn't.
羅斯還不知道
We'd appreciate it if no one told him yet.
對，請你們先別告訴他
Well,here it is.
就是這裡
A new place for a new Ross.
新羅斯的新家
I'll have you and the guys from work over, once it's furnished.
我一佈置好就請你和同事來坐
I must say it's nice to see you back on your feet.
很高興看到你重新振作
I am that, and the whole rage thing is definitely behind me.
我是振作了 脾氣暴躁的事都過去了
I wonder if it's time for you to rejoin our museum team?
你是不是該回館裡上班了？
That would be great.
那就太好了
I am totally ready to come back to work. I...
我已經準備好重回崗位，我…
What? No!
什麼？不
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Get off my sister!
別壓著我妹妹